## Leah Annitto

⊠leahannitto@amail.com **609-356-8861** LinkedIn

⊕ Portfolio

#### CAREER SUMMARY

#### Teacher/Researcher:

 Known for building and developing strong relationships, delivering successful student outcomes, and teacher collaboration, with strong organization skills

Experienced in aggregating, analyzing, and applying complex data to reach goals and assess student growth; skilled in creating organized plans to achieve complex goals; competent in resource and people management and

development

Sales Manager:

Demonstrates strengths in effective communication, marketing and sales data analysis

#### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

### Flatiron School Product Design Boot Camp New York, NY Certification | October 2023 UX Research/UI Design • Excellent skills in Figma and Adobe Suite

- Extensive knowledge of HTML/CSS
- · Track record of consistently delivering superb design work, showcasing a commitment to excellence and continuous improvement
- Proven skills in analyzing and interpreting user research findings- from surveys, interviews, and usability testingto generate actionable steps
- Adaptable in crossing between UX and UI design, leading to a holistic and seamless design process
- Communicate design concepts and
- specifications effectively to a team Conduct and coordinate usability interviews to gather feedback and
- insights for data-driven decision-making
  Provide feedback to team from users to achieve impeccable implementation of design features
- Design and develop a product from start to finish, prioritizing features and user research

# Relay Graduate School of Education New York, NY

Master of Arts | May 2021 Education, Dual Degree in Special and General Education Grades 1-6

Kenyon College Gambier, OH Bachelor of Arts | May 2016 Studio Art Major

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NYC DOE P.S. 138@189 M D75 K-2 8:1:1 ABA/VB Special Education Teacher September 2021-June 2023 | New York, NY

- Proven strong skills in organization, data aggregation, and self-motivation, with a strong track record of significant achievements, demonstrating a strong work ethic and results-driven approach
- Extensive experience in leading agile teams, fostering collaboration and driving successful project and student outcomes
- Created and facilitated curriculum for over 100 students with a proven ability to deliver high-quality work efficiently, resulting in successful and timely curriculum launches

Provided a structured learning environment demonstrating an eager and willing attitude, while exhibiting a

proactive, solution-oriented mindset Strategically collected and analyzed data for Individualized Education Programs, facilitating data-driven decision-making and planning based on student needs

Achievement First Bushwick Elementary First Grade Special Education Teacher July 2018-July 2021 | Brooklyn, NY

- Assisted in the transition from in-person to online learning during COVID-19
- Created new and data-driven online curriculum for more than 500 students
- Planned and implemented all aspects of the daily program, demonstrating a detail-oriented record of significant student achievements

Princeton University Sociology Department Research Assistant June 2016-July 2018 | Princeton, NJ

- Expertise in designing and conducting research studies, including qualitative and quantitative data collection and analysis
- Proven ability to manage research projects, including setting milestones, coordinating tasks, and meeting deadlines
- Effectively communicated research insights to research team lead
- Evaluated and interpreted complex data, applying logical reasoning to draw valid conclusions
- Collaborated cross-functionally across departments and teams